翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
This method works totally fine.
这种方法工作得很好
There's no reason you can't use the size and, in fact,
你没有理由不使用这个方法
I think it's pretty much the best solution.
我认为这几乎是最好的解决方案
However, we should, for the sake of just seeing the other pattern,
然而我们应该看看另一种模式
look at how this would be done iteratively even though I don't personally like it quite as much.
如何使用迭代实现，尽管我不喜欢这种
So to do that, I'm going to create a new method called iterative size.
创建一个新方法 interactiveSize
And it is going to return the size of the list using iteration.
它将使用迭代来返回 List 的大小
Or I'll just say no recursion.
或者说没有递归
And as before, I recommend that you try and guess
像以前一样，我建议你试着猜猜
what I'm about to do and then see how your answer compares to mine.
我接下来要做什么，然后比较你和我的答案
So in this case, a common pattern is to create a pointer variable.
在这种情况下，常见的模式是创建一个指针变量
So I'm going to call it p, and then I'm going to set it equal to this.
我把它命名为 p，然后设为 this
And I'm also going to set up a total size variable.
再设置一个 totalSize 变量
I'm going to set that equal to zero.
把它设为0
And then I'm going to say as long as p is not equal to null,
只要 p 不等于 null
I'm going to do the following.
就要做以下几件事
I'm going to say total size plus equals 1.
totalSize += 1
So it's going to get one larger.
所以它会变大
And then p is going to be equal to p.rest.
p = p.rest
And in that way, p is going to step along until finally total size is returned.
这样 p 就会继续前进，直到最终返回 totalSize
So let's try running this code.
试着运行这段代码
This will test it here.
在这里测试它
It worked.
成功了
And why?
为什么？
Let's try doing the visualization.
做一下可视化
So as before, we step forward until we get to iterate size.
像以前一样，前进直到 interactiveSize
And when that method kicks off, we're going to say,
当这个方法开始时，我们会说
you know what, p is going to be equal to this,
p 会等于 this
and then I'm going to set the total size equal to zero.
totalSize 设为0
Now as long as p is not null, I'm going to step through,
只要 p 不为 null，就持续向前
and I'm going to say, if the total size is larger
totalSize 变大
and p should step forward.
p 前进一步
We come back around.
又回来
Total size plus equals 1. p is steps 4.
totalSize 加1，p 前进
Finally, p is pointing at the last item on the list,
最后 p 指向 List 中的最后一项
so we could say total size plus 1,
totalSize 加1
p equals p.rest, in which case it will get set equal to null.
p = p.rest，在这种情况下，它将被设置为 null
And now we're done.
结束了
And we're going to return total size.
返回 totalSize
Now you could do something where you start to size off at 1,
你可以做些改变，比如从1开始计算
and you instead check p.rest does not equal to null.
检查 p.rest 不等于 null
Either approach is fine.
任何一种方法都可以
This is just the one I have happened to have picked.
我碰巧这样写
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
And that will give us an iterative size method.
这就是迭代的方法